{
    "id": "8e3c64fe6cac487ca4690fde370102ad",
    "title": "Comparative And Superlative",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "c4232397bdcb4189bf100fa2539286f9",
            "title": "Comparatives And Superlatives",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She is ……………………….. than her sister.",
                    "description": "Most adjectives of one syllable form the comparative by adding –er and superlative by adding –est.",
                    "answers": [
                        "prettier",
                        "more pretty",
                        "more prettier"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is ………………………… than that.",
                    "description": "If the positive adjective ends in -y, the comparative is made by replacing that -y with -i and adding -er.",
                    "answers": [
                        "more easy",
                        "more easier",
                        "easier"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I work hard but he works even …………………….",
                    "description": "Harder is the comparative form of hard. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "hard",
                        "harder",
                        "more hard"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was ……………………. than her parents.",
                    "description": "Adjectives of more than two syllables usually form the comparative by adding more to the positive. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "generouser",
                        "more generous",
                        "most generous"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was getting ……………………..",
                    "description": "The comparative is used when a change is implied. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "darker",
                        "dark",
                        "darkest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was the ………………………… day of his life.",
                    "description": "Happiest is the superlative form of happy.",
                    "answers": [
                        "happy",
                        "happier",
                        "happiest",
                        "most happy"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Solomon was the ………………….. of all men.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "wise",
                        "wiser",
                        "wisest",
                        "most wise"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Mark is ………………………… than his brothers.",
                    "description": "Richer is the comparative form of rich.",
                    "answers": [
                        "richer",
                        "more rich",
                        "most rich"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is ……………………. than his friends.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "smarter",
                        "more smart",
                        "more smarter"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is ……………………. than her brother.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "cleverer",
                        "more clever",
                        "most clever"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "His new home is ……………………….. than the previous one.",
                    "description": "Adjectives of more than two syllables form the comparative by adding -more",
                    "answers": [
                        "more spacious",
                        "most spacious",
                        "spaciouser"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The task was ……………………….. than I thought.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hard",
                        "harder",
                        "more hard"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}